Yehor Sereda

Golang Developer

Karmi'El, Israel (Able to relocate) +972 53 341-46-671 <u>entertainment.veks@gmail.com</u>

Telegram: <u>@entertainment_veks</u>

Github: entertainment-veks

GENERAL

I'm a **Golang Back-end developer** who migrated from Android (Java/Kotlin) 7 month ago. Got a half+ of a year of development web-apps near **blockchain and digital currency**. Also have 2.5 years of experience in developing android-apps. Also took a couple of courses from <u>Yandex.Practicum</u>. More details below **↓**

SKILLS

Golang: Go standard library, Gorilla, Go testing, Gogoc, Go database, Go vet + Go analyze (custom linters), Go Validation (ozzo/playground), FacebookGo inject, Loggers

Architecture: MVC, MVP, MVVM, SOLID, ACID, OOP, Go project layout

Android/General: Java Core, Kotlin Core, Hibernate, JPA, SQL, Firebase, JDBC, some Spring modules, REST, Websocket, Migrate, Docker, Docker Compose, Makefiles, Cron, MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, LiveData, Multithreading, Coroutines, Room, Dagger2, Koin, Hilt, NavUl, Rx basic, Glide, Gson, Android design components, Android Jetpack, Espresso, JUnit etc..

Language: Ukrainian, Russian - Native, English - Upper Intermediate, Hebrew - Beginner

PROJECTS

Golang:

<u>Demo Project Gophermart</u> - web service for accumulative loyalty system [still in progress]

Application X* - client for one of the digital currency exchange like $\underline{Binance}$ (in Company X*)

Application X* - client for one of the digital currency wallets storage like Metamask (in Company X*)

Android:

Demo Project "News App" - news app (June 2021)

GoDog - app for training dogs (in LeverX)

Application X* - shop-app for the biggest Germany customer (in LeverX)

Consulty - platform for expert consultations on all topics (in Sk.WebStudio)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Golang Developer - Company X* (Kyiv, remote) - product/outsource IT company

- Casual developer. Has finished a few projects.
- Generally was making clients for services which related with blockchain and digital currency like Binance, Metamask etc.
- Got knowledge of how blockchain and digital currency works, also got knowledge about microservice architecture and instruments like Kafka or websockets...
- from November 2021 till now

Android Developer - LeverX (Kyiv office, local) - outsource IT company

- Participated in few projects, mostly casual client-side android front-end apps.
- Was leading a small part of the team (2-5 developers).
- from March 2021 till November 2021

Android Developer - <u>Sk.WebStudio</u> (International, remote) - outsource IT company

- Casual developer. First experience in an international team.
- from July 2020 till March 2021

EDUCATION

Couple of courses "Go web" in Yandex.Practicum - as beta-tester

- A Tour of Go
- Go Web
- Go Web Advanced
- Multithreading in Go

Java Back-end in Mate Academy - IT academy

- Java Core
- JDBC + Hibernate
- Java Web
- Spring
- Multithreading

<u>Certificate</u> Android-development on <u>Coursera</u> - *quick start in Android-development.* Course from MIPT.

- Android components and interface elements
- Multithreading and networking in Android
- Android Application Architecture

Notes:

Application X - cannot tell the name of the application cause of NDA

Company X - cannot tell the name of the company cause of NDA